ABDALMJID MOHAMOUD



@ abdoshmhomed@gmail.com

Q 0928987662

Alklakla abo adam, Khartoum-Su

SKILLS

HTML, Css, Bootstrap

Php, laravel, Mysql, API

Git.Github

Microsoft office (word, PowerPoint, excel)

DATE BRITH

Date of Birth: 14/3/1997



vue js - flutter



Arbic

English

WEB DEVELOPER

Web developer specializing in Back-end developer. High capabilities in programming and designing websites using laravel & php with practical experience of more than two years I am looking for a job to gain more experience The process in programming and design and contribute to providing real additional and developing environments to which I belong.



EXPERIENCE

Hard target

15/1/2021 - 13/8/2021

Back-end developer laravel

I have high experience in developing websites professionally. I worked in Company hard target at work full time

CyanTeleology 9/9/2020 - 10/2/2020

Back-end developer php

ResUp 20/9/2021 - 25/9/2022

Back-end developer | Laravel

I worked in Company ResUp at work full time Backend developer

EDUCATION

University Neelain, Colleg of Computer Scince information technolegy 2015-2021

Bechelors Information system libarary

LIS

PERSONAL PROJECTS

E-commerice

https://softteech.com

Sales Of Point

http://sale-point.softteech.com

Contract Management

http://test-mangment.softteech.com/login

Profile

http://abdosh.softteech.com/



Summary

Web Developer specializing in **Back-end php/laravel**. Cooperate with Programmers' to create **clean code** and simple, intuitive interactions and experiences. Complete detailed programming and development tasks for front end public and internal websites as well as back- end server code.

Optimize usability